Hello world. It's been a while. I've
been busy creating Silver Daisy, a mini
hotel with three units and um I've
recorded about 50 hours worth of footage
and this video is not that video. This
is just simply a quick tour of the whole
place. I've taken a little break from
YouTube. I've personally had a a rough
time this year, but I do want to sit
down and edit all that 50 hours and show
you the whole process. But again, today
is just a quick tour. So, let's go check
out the logo. So, we had a local person
make this logo, silver daisy. And this
is hinoi wood, which is cypress. And
we've used a lot of hino throughout the
whole building, as we'll see. So, let's
go in through this entrance over here.
And basically, I just picked little
trees that we liked that would stay
evergreen that'll look good even in the
winter time. So, keep on. This is the
reception and laundry area. And my wife
made this map of the whole place. So we
have unit one, Kuromatsua, unit two,
Hinoi with its private Hinoi bath. And
we have Coyamaki, unit three. And we
have the laundry and reception area
where we are right here. That's you. And
down below the stairs, we got the deck,
zen garden, and the sauna. And if we go
over this way, 80 m, we have the parking
for guests if they need it. Uh, but
let's turn around this way to the
reception. So, this is our reception and
it's uh tiny as you can see. It looks
like a kind of a utility closet and
that's because guests aren't really
going to use this I believe when they're
checking in because you check in online
first. You get a code and then you would
punch the code in to the keypad and
enter.
So, what we do have though is storage
lockers. So, this is locker number
three, which is right over here. And so,
if you check in early and you want to
put your luggage somewhere while you're
going to sightsee, then you can use this
locker. Just put your luggage in there
and away you go. We have three lockers.
So, just
if you see a key,
a free key, then you take the key and
use the locker. Um, over here is our
laundry.
And you're also free to use the laundry.
Both the dryer. Yes, we have a dryer and
the washing machine. And over here is
the just for staff. You can kind of see
we have soaps and whatnot, rags. So,
that's for staff use. Uh, but come over
this way and you'll get the
really nice view of our lower level. So,
we have the barrel sauna and the zen
garden over there and stairs that uh
Algo and I painstakingly built
ourselves. We harvested the bamboo from
a bamboo forest and we set all the poles
in place. So, that was that was tough.
But right now, we're going to go to
Coyaki right over here. Um, and these
are actually made from the remains of
the flooring. So this is actually Hinoi
as well and uh my wife and I made these.
So she did the drawing and she I guess
kind of carved it with a mini router and
then I burned it in with a it's not
called a burning pen but I burned it. So
come over here.
So I'll say hino a lot. So this is hino
deck that was built not by me but by
professionals. And so here's the smart
lock. And so guest would punch in the
code.
It would open up and there you go.
And then if a guest wants to lock it,
all you do from the inside, you press it
and you lock it. So all right, let's
come on in.
And we're just going to change the the
filter because it's a bit dark. So this
is our smallest unit. So let's go over
here. This is a tatami with a This is
actually a bamboo table. And we have a
queen-siz bed. Currently our only
queen-sized bed. The rest of the beds
are futons. And this over here, this
wall, it's made of washi paper on the
top. And this is from Karasuyama,
a local area that makes the washi. And
then in the middle, we have these stones
which are called oyaishi. And we took
leftovers from a mine that they weren't
using and we put them in with our
architect
uh to make this pattern. And then that's
of course hinoi wood over there. Um and
there's actually hinoi wood under here
as well that the bed is on top of. Now
let's turn this all around this way.
So this is our little kitchenet.
And this is an iH. And uh I guess it's
pretty obvious. Toaster, microwave,
fridge. And we all have we also have a
water boiler and cups and cutlery and
everything. So basically, you can cook
everything. And look, the suction cup
has come off.
So we designed it so that you could
basically cook anything you want over
here if you need to. It's not just a
microwave and a fridge or not just a
fridge. So yeah, it's a full
kitchenette. And then over here we have
the bathroom. So this is the shower
room. And we got one that's a little bit
bigger than normal. So this one actually
has a bench so you can sit down and
relax with uh one of the two showers. Uh
but we thought it'd also be useful for
someone who has to take care of say
elderly parents and then it's easy to do
that or maybe you have some young kids
and um you can fit two people in here
quite easily. So that's why we got this
premium shower booth for you.
And um over here, this is a privacy
screen. So this is in case you're
staying with some people and you don't
want them to see you showering, but you
need to use the toilet, you can just use
this roll screen. So over here is a
Japanese toilet. And like any good
Japanese toilet, it has the heated
seats. Oh, here we go. It has the heated
seats and it'll wash your private parts.
And then over here they have the
controls. So you can see wash your bum,
wash your lady parts, small flush, big
flush, fan. Yeah. And the main thing
about this. So AO, if you go over that
way,
I'm going to take out this ladder
and go up to the loft.
So this also has a loft area. And
well, I should set the ladder properly.
>> So that's Ako. She's hiding. Oh
>> yeah.
>> So that's AO hiding over there. And this
ball here, this moon ball, that's
actually washi as well. So, like
handmade paper.
And
over here's the loft view. And out the
window, you'll get a nice view.
Well, that's of a house, but if you look
up, it's the mountain.
So, that's unit number three. And let's
go to unit number two now.
So, yeah, we put this little rack over
here for your clothes. And the last
little thing we have. So you can
use this to hang things if you want.
And now we're gonna go to unit two as
promised. Hinoi. All right.
These are our little bonesai which are
not doing too well. So I hope they're
still alive by the time my brother gets
here so he can check in on it.
This one's doing a little better. And
this one's
was actually near-death before, but it's
seems to have recovered. So, that's
good. Okay. So, this is the entrance to
Hino Key.
And this is the private deck for the
person or the group who's going to be
here. So, let me enter the code again.
Yeah. Come on in.
And so, we temporarily have this yellow
tape here. I don't know what we're going
to do with this to demark the line
between outside and inside, but here
outside stuff is okay. In here, it's
not. So, you have your slippers for the
inside and these slippers are for the
outside. So, we have a full kitchen over
here. And if you come this way, we have
IH stove and we actually have a
dishwasher.
This is kind of like an industrial
kitchen, commercial kitchen sink. And we
have a full-size fridge, microwave,
toaster, all the dishes you could want,
I think. So, you really could make
anything you want. And if you come over
this way,
this is a very large hino table. So, we
have five chairs here right now.
And you can actually separate this table
out if you want because you can use this
satami for sleeping. But if you want to
use it for I don't know, you can sit
down and relax here. Look at the view.
You can work from here. And let me just
bring this over this way.
This
is actually the model that the architect
originally made. And so we've done a few
modifications to this, but it's
basically all the same. So you have seen
number one over here
or this is number three, I should say.
Sorry. Room number three, Coyama Key.
And then you are currently
in
room number two, Hinoi.
And we're going to go to room one later
on and check it out. That's Kuromatsu.
So this wall, like the previous room, it
has the oya Ishi and the washi from
Karasyama. And these beams over here,
they're actually different from the
other room. If you noticed, you can
rewind back and check out those beams.
Those beams were hino. These beams are
SPF
spruce pine or fur from Canada actually.
And I don't know if you can see this,
but it says premium J, which means
premium Japanese. So Japanese always
want the premium wood from Canada. So
that's why it's premium J. So we've kind
of purposely left the markings on this
wood so you can kind of see a few
details on behind the scenes. And uh
let's go back over this way.
So, this is going to be hard for AO
walking around with the different
lighting. Um, but you see I I went down
a step and then over here you also go
down
>> you also go down another step. And so
the point is if you're sitting over here
or if you're sitting on the tatami mat
or if you're behind working in the
kitchen, you're all at the same eye
level. I didn't think of this. The
architect thought of this, so that's
what it is. And I forgot to showcase
this light over here. So, you turn it
on. Yeah. So, at night time, it's really
nice to have this big light. And you can
change the brightness level to to
however you like. And over here, we have
our kind of secret stairway. It's built
into the the cabinets here. And uh it
goes up to the loft area, which is the
main sleeping area. We originally didn't
have this post here, so it felt a bit
scary. So, we added this post in for
some security. And AO, if you want to
come walk up,
we can check out
the main loft over here.
>> Yeah, you have to watch her head. So,
this is actually a real
>> hazard.
I've hit my head like five times
already. Yeah, you can't see Ako, but
she's really ducking down to not hit it.
Um, I don't think I showcased the roll
screens, but um, yeah, took a while to
figure out what roll screens to get, but
I'm really happy with this one.
Although, I'm changing these out to have
ones that uh, don't have this dangly bit
because we don't need them in a lot of
the areas. But, yeah, we have a window
over here, and we also have a window
over there. And the original design
didn't have so many windows, but I don't
know, I'm Canadian. And I like to have a
lot of light and I also like to have air
flow. So we added extra windows. Uh but
we do have air con unit which can both
heat and cool. This is a new build so
hopefully in the winter this is enough
but if it's not we do have some
emergency gas heaters that we can plug
in from the inside and uh heat the
place. But yeah this is our main bedding
area over here. And this is I guess is
the safe zone where I mean I guess maybe
Dutch people this is not too safe. They
still have to bend down a bit but for me
uh it's safe.
Okay. And so let's go down back down
over this way. So you can see
right you have to duck down to go here.
So I don't know if you're staying for a
few days maybe that's a fun feature but
if you lived here all the time maybe
you'd find that really annoying. I don't
know, but uh on paper it looked really
cool. Um and uh I don't know. I'm really
curious to see if you come here to see
what you think about this. Uh I think
we're going to put up a light rail along
here though, just to kind of prevent
people from smacking their heads really
hard onto here, because there'll be a
light rail that goes along here. So you
would hit the light rail before you
smack in.
But yeah, I really really like this uh
all the different units because they all
have different features to them,
different look to them, even though
they're I guess all done by the same
architect, right? So, everyone has a
different feeling. So, you can go stay
at all three and see which one you like
best, I guess. Oh, and uh Okay, I'm
going to film AO coming down. You can
see
how it is.
>> There you go. See?
This is how you
>> There you go. She's fine.
[Music]
>> Yeah. Yeah. We definitely That's nice to
have.
>> Yeah. Okay, let's go to the bath, which
is just outside over there. That's the
nice Hinoi bath. That's something I
really, really wanted to have. Oh, I
mean, there's a toilet in here, but the
same toilet as the last one. So,
and this is the private bath. But before
we see the private bath, I'll show you
this little thing that we kind of
modified here. So, this is called a sur.
And if you want some extra privacy,
you could just hook it up here
and here and get a little bit more
privacy if you're sitting down over
there if you like. Private bath. Let's
enter.
So again, all the flooring that you see
like this is Hino. All right. So this is
the Hinoi wall bath because the bath is
not actually Hinoi itself. That'd be
kind of hard to maintain, but the walls
are hino. And so hopefully this proves
not hard to maintain, but we'll see. And
um I guess it's very bright, but I'll
show you an image after that. You get a
really great view during the daytime. At
night, you don't actually see that much.
And so, you would sit over here in the
bath and uh relax. Again, it would be
great if you could smell the hinoi. It's
such a It's nice.
Okay. And let me give you a view of the
outside. I'll take it over from Ako
here. Yeah. So, that's what it looks
like. Hey. All right. Okay, let's go
down to the
garden area down below in the sauna
area.
So, from this point onwards, everything
down below is basically DIY that mostly
Ako and I did. We had some help from
family members along the way, but uh
yeah, we're toing away
uh on this for months and Ako's just
going down the steps slowly because she
has to hold the camera, so
she can't go as fast as I can.
This is a leftover from when we tried to
put a tarp across, but when we did that,
the water started to pull and it was a
big mess. So, we're not currently using
this right now. Instead, we have the
tarps over here or the top tent canopies
over here that we uh started to use.
Yeah. So, again, this was Hinoi decks.
So, this garden over here, I just
randomly picked the plants. And this
mumiji over here, it's not doing so
well, but it it's been like this for
about a month or two, so it's surviving.
So, hopefully next year it'll be nicer.
the ume, like the Japanese plum. I don't
know what that that got eaten by, but
it's uh we'll see how it recovers. The
coyamaki looks a little bit yellow, so I
don't know. We just I just randomly
again picked all these plants and and
things. So, we'll see how they do in a
bit of time.
And um these rocks over here, I guess we
have these little rakes that we got to
do it, but I think when you do it by
hand, it actually works better for doing
doing a pattern. So my architect
actually did this where he's, you know,
doing a pattern with his hand
and it seems to be interesting. So yeah,
all these fences,
all these everything we basically did
ourselves. So that was a lot a lot of
work. Uh except for the sauna. We did
not build that ourselves. We got that
made in the prefecture of Gefu from wood
over there. And that's also Hinoi wood
as you might guess. And before we get to
the sauna, I'll just point out the
stairs. So this was the original
concrete that they had over there. So we
had to modify that or put the stairs on
top of this concrete. And um I had to
actually buy a hammer drill so I can
hammer down into the existing concrete
so I can put these poles in. And then we
use some uh instant cement.
I think that's what it's called to uh
set these into here. And then we took
rocks from around the yard that we dug
up and mortared those in. It was a whole
process. But uh I think it's pretty
sturdy now. But we'll guess we'll see in
a few years, right?
So
we'll come over here. So when you're
using the sauna,
you could put this and this is in use.
>> So in use,
>> but
you can enter. And so
this was a whole big thing of getting
this privacy, making this private
because to go in the sauna in Japan,
usually people go naked. So I wanted to
be able to do that. But we have the
units above so they could see in. So we
we put this finally came up with this
tent canopy here with these fabric walls
so that you can't see. And then we had
this fence in place with more suit so
you can't see. But it's also you could
take a shower or a cold bath if you want
to without wearing your sauna wear
because you would get pretty soaked with
that. But uh yeah, this is a garden hose
hookup as you can see. Very uh DIY.
And the bath would fill up using this.
You want to empty the bath, we have the
little wrench here or tweezers,
pinchers, I don't know what you call
this. And you can open the cap over
there if you want to. So, this is just a
garden hose that you could use to shower
off without any soap. Uh, you know, in
the summertime. In the winter time, it's
going to be too cold. It'll be icy, so
you can't use the shower. Um,
but this is, uh, I don't know how to
pronounce it. Loy sauna. Lolu sauna. In
Japanese, it's royu.
>> Roio sauna.
>> Roio sana. And so, let's come into the
sauna.
Tada. And it's going to be dark, right?
Could I?
>> So, this is an electric sauna. You just
dial it in. Goes for 4 hours.
And if you want to get some steam, dip
it in the water, pour it on the rocks.
Yeah, the smell in this is just amazing.
And over here, we had to modify this
with some drywall cuz the fire
department said it wasn't safe enough.
So, we we put that in and we got some
permission to operate.
But yeah, I love saunas and I really
hope if you come here and you like
saunas that you try it out and you enjoy
it as well. So, let's go back out. Oh,
so over here we planted bamboo. And uh
some people thought we're crazy for
planting bamboo cuz it could spread out
quite quickly and rapidly. Like we only
planted this a few months ago, but you
can see we have new plants coming out
here. And these are new shoots over
here. Uh there's lots of new shoots, but
we actually have a plastic
barrier
um all around it that's really really
hard that's meant for bamboo to protect
it from roots popping out. So hopefully
we won't have that problem of them
popping out, but we we will we will see.
We will see. And over here, we also
built this little privacy fence to block
us from that area as well.
And now, let's go up back to the top.
So, it's uh fall now. It's October. What
is the date we're filming now? Is it the
13th? Yeah, it's October 13th.
And uh it's the busiest time right now
because the changing of the leaves is
the really popular time in Niko. Unit
number one, Kuromatsu. That's getting
prepared right now. So we're going to go
out to the exterior and check around
outside. So let's go this way.
So I know the lighting is changing.
That's making Ako very nervous.
So here
anyway, what is this thing? Look at this
thing. It just attacked me.
>> I don't know. Nice.
[Music]
>> I don't
>> Why did it attack me?
>> That was scary.
>> So So yeah, we're out in nature over
here. All right, so
>> yeah, this is our little uh parking lot.
It can only really fit K cars in here.
It won't fit like a compact car or other
types, but it's um when you see
something parked in here, it's really
quite something because it's you're
right on the edge of everything. So, I'm
actually going to build
uh some safety barrier around here to to
help. But, uh let's go on over this way.
So, this is the front. So, we planted a
little little tiny garden here in the
front.
And let's just check out this side, the
exciting infrastructure side. So, this
is the solar panel control unit. And um
I don't think you saw it in any of the
shots, the solar panels, because you
have to be from above to see it, but uh
if you've never seen it, we can throw up
the drone and give you a look. Um, and
these are called Eco1s.
And these are a combination unit where
it uses both gas but also these I
believe these are compressors and this
is just kind of like the same technology
as the aircon unit. So these are like
heat pumps, right? So heat pump will
heat up the tank in here and store
water. So in combination with the solar
panels, you pretty much get like free
heating of the water, but if you end up
using a lot of water, it has the gas
here that can make sure you don't end up
in the middle of winter without any hot
water. So it's a combined system here.
And this is just a smaller version of it
right there. So one, two, three. This is
all called Eco1.
And then these tanks over here, these
are propane gas and it's used for the
dryer. It's used for the water heaters
and it's also going to be used in an
emergency if the air con units are not
enough to heat up in the winter time.
And um I guess the last part about the
exterior over here is just kind of for
like staff usage. We have landscaping
equipment and the uh recycling and
garbage. And actually all like down this
slope is our property as well, but you
can't build on it. So it's just slope.
Yeah. Let's go to unit number three.
Back around this way. We're at the final
stop of the tour, Kurroatsu. So come on
in.
Here we go. Whoa. Maybe not.
>> All right. So, come on in.
Again, the hinoi floors and the tatami,
the washi moon. And let's see the other
side, which is the kitchen. So, this is
our little kitchenette with everything
that was in room number three. And up
there, if you look way up, that's the
loft where people will mainly sleep. So,
I'm going to grab the ladder in a
second, but first I'm going to go here.
And they have the same sink and shower
booth over here. And this is the toilet
over here. All right,
let's grab this ladder. So, the ladder's
stored over here. And we're actually
building some stairs. So, it's going to
look like this, I think, next week. So,
by time you come, it'd be like this. So,
we're going to build like a permanent
stairway. But for now,
we have this ladder.
Put it in like that. And I'll go up and
then I'll grab the camera from that go.
Okay.
Here we go.
>> Okay. So, this is the view from the
loft. And I just climbed up these stairs
or this ladder.
And here we go. The loft where you could
sleep two people or maybe three. We're
thinking about putting a queen bed in
here, but we'll see.
So, again, with this window, I put this
window in so you can get a nice view and
hear the sounds of the river and get a
nice breeze if you want. So, here's the
other view of the loft. And then you can
look down and see
the tatami where you can also sleep. So
we did make sure that you can fit two
futons down there and you can sleep two
people if you would like. So if you want
you can get like four people in this
unit. So that's it for the tour of
Silver Daisy Stay Nico. It's been a long
process I think since we first started
trying to buy the land. It's been almost
two years now and it's been yeah long
and tough but uh it's done and we had
our first guests from France come in two
days ago at the same time as some
Japanese guests as well and so that was
cool to finally have some people out but
we're now open for business so hopefully
you can come and enjoy that'd be really
nice and um yeah I'll have a full video
of the whole making of process out
sometime but it's uh 50 hours of footage
So, probably will take a while to edit.
Uh, so give me a little bit of time for
that. Uh, but yeah, as always, thanks
for watching. See you next time. Peace.